[{"questionId":"0bc554e4-5c75-4c4d-89a3-28cc4613e0f3","author":"peter6","questionTitle":"Maven Out of Memory Build Failure","questionTimestamp":"2022","questionText":"My maven compile fails.I just bumped up my heap to 3 GB. Also, I only changed 2-3 minor lines of code, so I don't understand this 'out of memory' error.I tried the poster's comment by changing my failed module's pom.xml. But I got the same maven build error","questionTag":["Build","Maven","Memory"],"answers":[{"answerId":"123","author":"peter","answerTimestamp":"2022","answerText":"asdsad"},{"answerId":"0fcfaaf8ba2745c9bab1807b679f6865","author":"peter2","answerTimestamp":"2032","answerText":"asdsad"}]},{"questionId":"74ef6991-a3e9-4cf5-bde4-73f6f7dac2ff","author":"john2","questionTitle":"New question4","questionTimestamp":"2022","questionText":"Failed to establish a connection in pgAdmin","questionTag":["TagA","TagD","testTagB"],"answers":[{"answerId":"123","author":"peter","answerTimestamp":"2022","answerText":"asdsad"},{"answerId":"6addf75bfdd14a059403709da027cabd","author":"peter2","answerTimestamp":"2032","answerText":"asdsad"}]},{"questionId":"542e753f-94b6-415a-b116-873760749707","author":"peter4","questionTitle":"New question4","questionTimestamp":"2022","questionText":"Failed to establish a connection in pgAdmin","questionTag":["TagA","TagD","testTagB"],"answers":[]},{"questionId":"e9e7058d-fad4-4b09-9b7e-24165e370738","author":"pucker3","questionTitle":"New question1","questionTimestamp":"2021","questionText":"Failed to establish a connection in docker","questionTag":["TagA","TagD","testTagB"],"answers":[]},{"questionId":"0d1f7b8a-499c-45b3-b95d-f13db7723da3","author":"u2","questionTitle":"Maven Out of Memory Build Failure","questionTimestamp":"2021-09-08","questionText":"My maven compile fails.I just bumped up my heap to 3 GB. Also, I only changed 2-3 minor lines of code, so I don't understand this 'out of memory' error.I tried the poster's comment by changing my failed module's pom.xml. But I got the same maven build error","questionTag":["Build","Maven","Memory"],"answers":[{"answerId":"54050baa12e0457cb498dad66d4e116c","author":"peter12","answerTimestamp":"09-09-2020","answerText":"I used export MAVEN_OPTS=-Xmx512m -XX:MaxPermSize=350m and worked."},{"answerId":"461930366ace44e2b86b691ba62319f1","author":"adam_p","answerTimestamp":"10-10-2020","answerText":"Forking the compile process might be not the best idea, because it starts a second process which ignores MAVEN_OPTS altogether, thus making analysis more difficult.So I would try to increase the Xmx by setting the MAVEN_OPTS"}]},{"questionId":"05da7f29-8274-4d68-a854-66f7054395c5","author":"u2","questionTitle":"Maven Out of Memory Build Failure","questionTimestamp":"2021-09-08","questionText":"My maven compile fails.I just bumped up my heap to 3 GB. Also, I only changed 2-3 minor lines of code, so I don't understand this 'out of memory' error.I tried the poster's comment by changing my failed module's pom.xml. But I got the same maven build error","questionTag":["Build","Maven","Memory"],"answers":[{"answerId":"123425a668474cf79b24c86734389210","author":"peter12","answerTimestamp":"09-09-2020","answerText":"I used export MAVEN_OPTS=-Xmx512m -XX:MaxPermSize=350m and worked."},{"answerId":"33ff7cc4ef084a279db9ad8289ffec29","author":"adam_p","answerTimestamp":"10-10-2020","answerText":"Forking the compile process might be not the best idea, because it starts a second process which ignores MAVEN_OPTS altogether, thus making analysis more difficult.So I would try to increase the Xmx by setting the MAVEN_OPTS"}]},{"questionId":"8b2dc859-cfcc-4ff2-a182-f0ab52272a53","author":"u2","questionTitle":"New question by u2","questionTimestamp":"2021-09-08","questionText":"Failed to establish a connection in docker","questionTag":["TagA","TagD","testTagB"],"answers":[]},{"questionId":"34323efc-f560-46bc-80b1-c6ba2e60e066","author":"peter2","questionTitle":"New question4","questionTimestamp":"2022","questionText":"Failed to establish a connection in pgAdmin","questionTag":["TagA","TagD","testTagB"],"answers":[{"answerId":"123","author":"peter","answerTimestamp":"2022","answerText":"asdsad"},{"answerId":"4517e3df6e4f40e7b949c662f5688913","author":"peter2","answerTimestamp":"2032","answerText":"asdsad"}]},{"questionId":"d581c8a7-245c-4584-813a-65bd3879bc7d","author":"peter6","questionTitle":"New question4","questionTimestamp":"2022","questionText":"Failed to establish a connection in pgAdmin","questionTag":["TagA","TagD","testTagB"],"answers":[{"answerId":"123","author":"peter","answerTimestamp":"2022","answerText":"asdsad"},{"answerId":"e3137d8ae52c4ffe87e455ac68008af1","author":"peter2","answerTimestamp":"2032","answerText":"asdsad"}]},{"questionId":"b6c7c279-b313-4b12-9a98-bb15dcaa4246","author":"peter5","questionTitle":"New question4","questionTimestamp":"2022","questionText":"Failed to establish a connection in pgAdmin","questionTag":["TagA","TagD","testTagB"],"answers":[{"answerId":"123","author":"peter","answerTimestamp":"2022","answerText":"asdsad"},{"answerId":"06efe2c1621b4c5fb4b9ea8aa746ab8d","author":"peter2","answerTimestamp":"2032","answerText":"asdsad"}]}]